this is the inventory recording for November 30th 2025 we're gonna have
quite a few different counts tonight the first one we're gonna do is gonna be in
my truck so we have four six packs of squealing pig Sauvignon Blanc wine two
bottles of scarpetta 12 bottles of margarita mix those 750 milliliter ones
of the stirrings again 12 margarita 12 watermelon stirrings mixer 24 Mark
caseres cava 750 milliliter bottles this looks like Prosecco again it's spelled
M-A-R-Q-U-E-S Marquez is how it looks de caseres de C-A-C-E-R-E-S Marquez de
caseres six more bottles of watermelon mixer half of a bottle of erradura ultra
agnejo the second place that we're gonna count is going to be the walk-in cooler
so in the walk-in there's one full keg of 38 beach blonde again those are half
barrels and then everything else is six barrels three six barrels of Paradise
Park two perfect plane yachtside three Kona big wave add one more perfect plane
yachtside add one more Kona big wave and we have two kegs of Stella Artois okay
so each one of these cases of fresh Victor's juices is two 64 fluid ounce
bottles so when I say a case that's what it is so there are four cases of let's
see this is for again sorry four cases of the cactus pear and pomegranate
cocktail mixer and then two cases of the fresh Victor's cucumber lime again two cases of those
the next place we're gonna count is the inside bar okay so inside bar we have four fifths of
a bottle of Colonel E.H. Taylor small batch we have a quarter of a bottle of Pappas Pilar
the sherry cask one can of watermelon high noon one can of Michelob Ultra one can of Miller Light
one can of Coors Light one can of Pacifico one can of yingling one can of athletic upside Don
half of a bottle of the Eagle rare aged ten years because in the past we have had twelve
this is the ten year three quarters of a bottle of red excuse me call it four fifths of a bottle
of Redwood Empire 90% of a bottle of Nickters 75% of a bottle of the shaker red blend full
bottle of canoe Ridge Merlot 80% of a bottle of windstorm Chardonnay 75% of a bottle of Campari
a full bottle of Campesino aged rum 80% of a bottle of Campesino silver rum 95% of a bottle
of Jack Daniel's 80% of a bottle of Myers aged rum full bottle of sham board 75% of a bottle of
Mark 80% of a bottle of Jim Beam 80% of a bottle of Tullamore Dew a third of a bottle of gray goose
and this bottle is 750 milliliters full bottle of crop lemon full bottle of Parrot Bay coconut
rum half of a bottle of Casamigos silver full bottle of grenadine half of a bottle of fireball
90% of a bottle of farmers gin one full bottle of crop cucumber vodka quarter of a bottle of
Grand Marnier full bottle of caravela limoncello another quarter of a bottle of Casamigos quarter
of a bottle of Tanqueray half of a bottle of Milagro Reposado half of a bottle of Parrot
Bay coconut rum half of a bottle of Parrot Bay white rum 75% of a bottle of Yahweh 90% of a bottle
of Siete Mesterios mezcal 25% of a bottle of Pueblo Viejo 20% of a bottle of triple sec
three-quarters of a bottle of Wheatley's vodka oh also in storage so let's add this to this
count as well in storage we have a full 12 bottle case of Wheatley's so let's add that to the count
16 cans of Miller Lite 22 cans of Yingling 5 cans of athletic non-alcoholic beer 7 cans of
again for all the canned stuff I need a total can amount for each one one can of high-rise
pineapple 12 cans of Coors Light 7 cans of Pacifico 24 cans of high noon 6 cans of ginger beer
4 bottles of Scarpetta 2 bottles of Squealing Pig 1 bottle of Bloody Mary Mix 1 bottle of
of Marca de Caceres 1 bottle of 30a Chardonnay 1 bottle of Windstorm Chardonnay
half of a bottle of Pueblo Viejo 90% of a bottle of Yahweh 25% of a bottle of Eagle
Rare 10 year aged quarter of a bottle of E.H. Taylor half of a bottle of Parrot Bay white rum
half of a bottle of Myers aged rum a quarter of a bottle of Siete Mestadios mezcal a full bottle
of triple sec a half bottle of crop cucumber vodka a half bottle of Wheatley's excuse me make that
60% of a bottle of Wheatley's instead of a half and then a half of a 750 milliliter bottle of
Grey Goose 20% of a bottle of Woodford half of a bottle of Jim Beam a full bottle of Mikters 80%
of a bottle of Crown 25% of a bottle of Hendrick's Gin 90% of a bottle of Casamigos 25% of a bottle
of Milagro Reposado a full bottle of Milagro Silver 85% of a bottle of Blanton's 80% of a bottle
of Caravella 98% of a bottle of Maker's Mark 80% of a bottle of Grand Gala 95% of a bottle
of Bowles elderflower liqueur half of a bottle of Blue Curacao 10% of a bottle of Jack Daniels
half of a bottle of Tanqueray
half of a bottle of Jameson half of a keg of Paradise Park a full keg of Stella Artois
full keg of Kona Big Wave all right now starting on the back bar we have three bottles of Tahin
24 Coors lights 13 athletic non-alcoholic beers
16 Miller lights
10 Yinglings
14 Pacificos 24 Michelob Ultras
16 one bottle of Blue Agave
two bottles of cream of coconut
excuse me three total bottles of cream of coconut at the back bar again that's three
um two bottles of strawberry puree
three cans of ginger beer
so
3.8 bottles of mojito mix plus one more bottle of mojito mix
four and a half bottles of watermelon cocktail mix again that's four and a half bottles of
watermelon mix two bottles of margarita mix
one bottle of squealing pig Sauvignon Blanc five bottles of
of scarpetta
four bottles of 30a chardonnay
one bottle of windstorm chardonnay
uh
two and a half bottles of carter's lot rosé
one bottle of sonoma coutrere wine white wine one more bottle of carter's lot rosé
one bottle of 30a rosé two bottles of charles de fer prosecco three bottles of marca de caseres
prosecco one more bottle of windstorm chardonnay
windstorm chardonnay
24 pack of micolob ultra 24 pack of yingling 12 pack of miller light 12 pack of pacifico
12 pack of coarse light full bottle of jack daniels
two full bottles of parrot bay white rum
two and a half bottles of parrot bay coconut rum full bottle of wheatleys full 750 milliliter
bottle of gray goose three full bottles of yave coconut tequila if i don't say you know if i just
say bottles that means it's full if i don't specify the percentage
33 percent of a bottle of fireball two bottles of crown royal
85 percent of a bottle of tia maria espresso coffee liqueur
full bottle of jameson full bottle of sieta misterios mezcal full bottle of wheatleys
1.75 bottles of jim beam full bottle of makers mark full bottle of milagro reposado
10 percent of a bottle of rumple mints 25 percent of a bottle of jagermeister
75 percent of a bottle of rumple mints full bottle of jalapeno simple syrup
75 percent of a bottle of romano romana amaro full bottle of hendrix gin
full bottle of campesino silver rum half of a bottle of campesino aged rum
33 percent of a bottle of nocello
walnut liqueur 85 percent of a bottle of tulamore dew 25 percent of a bottle of
apparol full bottle of farmers gin
24 cans of myckelope ultra
13 cans of greaton 30a gosey 24 more cans of myckelope ultra
got a got a four pack of mom waters 12 pack of pacifico two four packs of red bull
12 cans of yingling
13 cans of high rise pineapple
six cans of red bull regular three cans of red bull low sugar
20 mom waters so 20 cans of mom water got a high noon one can of high noon
got one full bottle of the shaker red blend
full bottle of canoe ridge 75 percent of a bottle of canoe ridge full bottle of
apparol full bottle of bloody mary mix full bottle of jalapeno simple syrup
one other full bottle of canoe ridge merlot we also need to add two 12 bottle cases of 30a rose
a we also need to add two 12 bottle cases of 30a pinot noir and two 12 bottle cases of 30a
cabernet Sauvignon
now we are doing the upstairs dry goods slash just storage area count so this is going to be
the last count we have two
six bottle cases of crop organic cucumber vodka and those are one liter bottles
so between the two cases 12 total one liter bottles of crop organic cucumber vodka
then add three singular bottles of crop cucumber vodka on top of that
three bottles of canoe ridge merlot seven bottles of gearbox pinot noir
nine bottles of the shaker red blend one bottle of eridura reposado
tequila one bottle of eridura on yeho tequila
and one bottle of eridura silver tequila
we have this bottle of eridura legend it says tequila on yeho
it's a 750 milliliter bottle it looks super nice it comes in this black case thing
eight bottles of scarpetta four bottles of 30a chardonnay eight bottles of windstorm chardonnay
two bottles of windstorm cabernet
of windstorm cabernet
13 bottles of canoe ridge merlot six bottles of marca de caseres
27 bottles of marca de caseres so on top of the six that i just counted
nine bottles of stirring's watermelon cocktail mix
eight bottles of mojito mix
12 bottles of bloody mary mix
11 bottles of cream of coconut
excuse me
only seven bottles of cream of coconut upstairs only seven
10 bottles of strawberry puree four bottles of blue agave i have four four packs of high
rise pineapple again i just need the total can count on those
14 bottles of grenadine
16 bottles of tahini
17 six bottles of angostura bitters i've got a 24 pack of ginger beer
another 12 pack of ginger beer
two six packs or excuse me two cases of six bottles of watermelon cocktail mix
24 pack of yingling 12 packs of pacifico 424 packs of make globe ultra one 12 pack of core's
light two 12 packs of corona extra cans two 12 packs of athletic
the na beer two four packs of red bull regular
five four packs of red bull sugar-free i'm not sure what i said for the normal red bull but those
are four packs i think i might have said something else but there's two four packs of red bull
upstairs all day that's all we have is two four packs of red bull regular and then again we have
and then again we have five of the sugar-free red bull 13 bottles of pueblo viejo
nine bottles of yave coconut tequila one bottle of casamigos
11 bottles of siete misterios mezcal
11 bottles of milagros silver two bottles of parrot bay white rum seven bottles of parrot bay
coconut rum 14 bottles of triple sec
10 bottles of blue curacao and the triple sec and the blue curacao both of those are the mr boston
mr boston and again remember the margarita mix and the mojito mix and the watermelon mix
those are all under liquor and they're called like bar mix comma watermelon bar mix comma margarita
bar mix comma mojito then we have two bottles of papas palar the sherry cask
five bottles of caravela limoncello five bottles of campesino silver rum
two bottles of grand marnier five bottles of bowls elderflower liqueur
nine bottles of rumple mints
seven bottles of romana amaro five bottles of crown royal
11 bottles of meyers original dark rum three bottles of maker's mark five bottles of
jim beam one bottle of tolamore dew one bottle of jaeger
eight bottles of jack daniels one bottle of fireball
nine bottles of grand gala three bottles of woodford
eight bottles of tanker a
six bottles of jamison
10 bottles of jaeger meister
four point nine bottles of apparel two bottles of tia maria coffee liqueur one bottle of nacello
walnut liqueur three quarters of a bottle of ferretti espresso coffee liqueur two point eight bottles of campari