This is the inventory recording for November 30th, 2025.
24 bottles Squealing Pig Sauvignon Blanc.
2 bottles Scarpetta.
12 bottles Margarita Mix.
12 bottles Watermelon Mixer.
Both the Margarita and the Watermelon are the Stirrings Mixers.
24 bottles of Marcus de Caceres.
And that's spelled M as in Mark, A, R, Q, U, E, S, D, C as in Cat, A, C as in Cat, E, R, E, S.
6 more bottles of the Watermelon Mixer.
Half of a bottle of the Aradura Ultra Agnejo.
Second location is the Walk-In Cooler.
One keg of the 30A Beach Blonde.
3 kegs Paradise Park.
2 kegs Perfect Plane Yachtside.
3 kegs Kona Big Wave.
1 keg Perfect Plane.
1 keg Kona Big Wave.
2 kegs Stella Artois.
4 cases of Cactus Pear and Pomegranate Cocktail Mixer.
2 cases of Fresh Victor's Cucumber Lime Juice.
Next location is the Inside Bar.
80% of a bottle of Colonel E.H. Taylor.
25% of Papas Pilar.
1 can High Noon.
1 can Michelob Ultra.
1 can Miller Lite.
1 can Coors Lite.
1 can Pacifico.
1 can Yingling.
1 can Athletic Upside Down.
50% of a bottle of Eagle Rare.
75% of a bottle of Redwood Empire.
Full bottle of Mikters.
75% of a bottle of Shaker Red Blend.
Full bottle of Canoe Ridge.
80% of a bottle of Windstorm Chardonnay.
75% of a bottle of Campari.
A full bottle of Campesino Aged Rum.
80% of a bottle of Campesino Silver Rum.
95% of a bottle of Jack Daniels.
80% of a bottle of Myers Aged Rum.
Full bottle of Shambord.
75% of a bottle of Maker's Mark.
80% of a bottle of Jim Beam.
80% of a bottle of Tullamore Dew.
33% of a bottle of Parrot Bay Coconut Rum.
50% of a bottle of Casamigo Silver.
Full bottle of Grenadine.
50% of a bottle of Fireball.
90% of a bottle of Farmer's Gin.
Full bottle of Crop Cucumber Vodka.
25% of a bottle of Grand Marnier.
Full bottle of Caravella Limoncillo.
25% of a bottle of Casamigos.
25% of a bottle of Tanqueray.
50% of a bottle of Milagro Repasado.
50% of a bottle of Parrot Bay Coconut Rum.
50% of a bottle of Parrot Bay White Rum.
75% of a bottle of Yave.
90% of a bottle of Siete Mestedios Mezcal.
25% of a bottle of Puebla Viejo Tequila.
20% of a bottle of Triple Sec.
75% of a bottle of Wheatley's Vodka.
12 bottles of Wheatley's Vodka.
16 cans of Miller Lite.
22 cans of Yingling.
5 cans of Athletic Non-Alcoholic Beer.
12 cans of Coors Light.
7 cans of Pacifico.
24 cans of High Noon.
6 cans of Ginger Beer.
4 bottles of Scarpetta.
2 bottles of Squealing Pig.
1 bottle of Bloody Mary Mix.
1 bottle of Marques de Caceres Prosecco.
1 bottle of 30A Chardonnay.
1 bottle of Windstorm Chardonnay.
50% of a bottle of Pueblo Viejo Tequila.
90% of a bottle of Yave Coconut Tequila.
20% of a bottle of Yave Coconut Tequila.
25% of a bottle of Eagle Rare.
25% of a bottle of E.H. Taylor.
50% of a bottle of Parrot Bay White Rum.
Half of a bottle of Meyer's Aged Rum.
25% of a bottle of Siete Misterios Mezcal.
Full bottle of Triple Sec.
50% or half.
50% of a bottle of...
Sorry, let me start over with the count for this product.
50% of a bottle of Crop Cucumber Vodka.
I made a mistake where I said half of a bottle and I kind of stumbled over my words.
That just needs to be 50% of a bottle of Crop Cucumber Vodka.
Now on to the next item.
50% of a bottle of Wheatly's.
50% of a 750ml bottle of Grey Goose.
20% of a bottle of Woodford.
50% of a bottle of Jim Beam.
A full bottle of Michter's.
80% of a bottle of Crown Royal.
25% of a bottle of Hendrick's Gin.
90% of a bottle of Casamigos.
25% of a bottle of Caravella Limoncillo.
A full bottle of Maker's Mark.
80% of a bottle of Grand Gala.
95% of a bottle of Bowls Elderflower Liqueur.
50% of a bottle of Blue Curacao.
10% of a bottle of Jack Daniel's.
Half of a bottle of Tanqueray.
Again, half is the same thing as 50%.
50% of a bottle of Jameson.
50% of a keg of Paradise Park.
One keg Stella Artois.
One keg Kona Big Wave.
Next location is the back bar.
Four bottles of Taheem, the spice.
24 Coors Lights.
13 athletic non-alcoholic beers.
16 Miller Lights.
10 Yinglings.
14 Pacificos.
24 Michelob Ultras.
16 bottles of Agave.
Two bottles of Cream of Coconut.
One bottle of Cream of Coconut.
Two bottles Strawberry Puree.
Three cans Ginger Beer.
3.8 bottles of Mojito Mix.
One bottle of Mojito Mix.
4.5 bottles of Watermelon Mixer.
Two bottles Margarita Mix.
One bottle Squealing Pig.
Five bottles Scarpetta.
Four bottles 30A Chardonnay.
One bottle Windstorm Chardonnay.
Two and a half bottles of Carter's Lot Rosé.
One bottle of Sonoma Coutrere White Wine.
One bottle of Carter's Lot Rosé.
One bottle of 30A Rosé.
Two bottles of Charles de Fer Prosecco.
Three bottles of Marcus de Caceres Prosecco.
One bottle of Windstorm Chardonnay.
24 cans of Michelob Ultra.
24 cans of Yingling.
12 cans of Miller Lite.
12 cans of Pacifico.
12 packs of Coors Lite.
A full bottle of Jack Daniels.
Two bottles of Parrot Bay White Rum.
Two and a half bottles of Parrot Bay Coconut Rum.
A full bottle of Wheat Lees.
A full 750ml bottle of Grey Goose.
Three full bottles of Yahweh Coconut Tequila.
33% of a bottle of Fireball.
Two bottles of Crown Royal.
85% of a bottle of Tia Maria Espresso Coffee Liqueur.
Full bottle of Jameson.
Full bottle of Siete Mestedios Mezcal.
Full bottle of Wheat Lees.
1.75 bottles of Jim Beam.
Full bottle of Maker's Mark.
Full bottle of Milagro Reposado.
10% of a bottle of Rumple Mints.
25% of a bottle of Jägermeister.
75% of a bottle of Rumple Mints.
Full bottle of Jalapeno Simple Syrup.
75% of a bottle of Romano Amaro.
Full bottle of Hendrix Gin.
Full bottle of Campesino Silver.
Half, excuse me, 50% of a bottle of Campesino Aged Rum.
33% of a bottle of Nocello.
Walnut Liqueur.
85% of a bottle of Tullamore Dew.
25% of a bottle of Aperol.
A full bottle of Farmer's Gin.
24 cans of Michelob Ultra.
13 cans of Grayton 30A Goze.
And that's spelled G-R-A-Y-T-O-N.
G-O-S-E.
24 cans Michelob Ultra.
4 cans Mom Water.
12 cans Pacifico.
8 cans Red Bull Regular.
12 cans Yingling.
13 cans High Rise.
6 cans Regular Red Bull.
3 cans Red Bull Low Sugar.
20 cans Mom Water.
1 full bottle of Shaker Red Blend.
Full bottle of Canoe Ridge.
75% of a bottle of Canoe Ridge.
Full bottle of Aperol.
Full bottle of Bloody Mary Mix.
Full bottle of Jalapeno Simple Syrup.
Full bottle of Canoe Ridge Merlot.
24 bottles of 30A Rose.
24 bottles of 30A Pinot Noir.
24 bottles of 30A Cabernet Sauvignon.
Next location is upstairs.
12 1 liter bottles of Crop Organic Cucumber Vodka.
3 bottles of Crop Cucumber Vodka.
3 bottles Canoe Ridge Merlot.
7 bottles Gearbox Pinot Noir.
9 bottles Shaker Red Blend.
1 bottle of Eridura Reposado.
1 bottle of Eridura Añejo Tequila.
1 bottle of Eridura Silver Tequila.
The Eridura Legend bottle in the black case.
8 bottles Scarpetta.
4 bottles 30A Chardonnay.
8 bottles Windstorm Chardonnay.
2 bottles of Windstorm Cabernet.
13 bottles Canoe Ridge Merlot.
6 bottles Marques de Caceres.
27 bottles Marques de Caceres.
9 bottles Stirrings Watermelon Mixer.
8 bottles Mojito Mix.
12 bottles Bloody Mary Mix.
11 bottles Cream of Coconut.
10 bottles Strawberry Puree.
4 bottles of Agave.
16 cans of High Rise Pineapple.
14 bottles Grenadine.
16 bottles Tahin.
17 bottles of Angostura Bitters.
24 cans of Ginger Beer.
12 cans of Ginger Beer.
12 bottles of Watermelon Mixer.
24 cans Yingling.
12 cans Pacifico.
96 cans Micolob Ultra.
12 cans Coors Light.
24 cans Corona.
24 cans Athletic Non-Alcoholic Beer.
8 cans Red Bull Regular.
20 cans Red Bull Sugar Free.
13 bottles Pueblo Viejo.
9 bottles Yave Coconut Tequila.
1 bottle Casamigos.
11 bottles Siete Misterios Mezcal.
11 bottles Milagros Silver.
2 bottles Parrot Bay White Rum.
7 bottles Parrot Bay Coconut Rum.
14 bottles Triple Sec.
10 bottles Blue Curacao.
5 bottles Caravella Limoncello.
5 bottles Campesino Silver Rum.
2 bottles Grand Marnier.
5 bottles Bowls Elderflower Liqueur.
9 bottles Rumple Mints.
7 bottles Romana Amaro.
5 bottles Crown Royal.
11 bottles Meyers Original Dark Rum.
3 bottles of Maker's Mark.
5 bottles of Jim Beam.
1 bottle of Tullamore Dew.
1 bottle of Jaeger.
8 bottles of Jack Daniels.
1 bottle of Fireball.
9 bottles of Grand Gala.
3 bottles of Woodford.
8 bottles of Take Array.
6 bottles of Jameson.
10 bottles of Jaegermeister.
5 bottles of Aperol.
2 bottles of Tia Maria Coffee Liqueur.
1 bottle of Nocello Walnut Liqueur.
75% of a bottle of Ferretti Espresso Coffee Liqueur.
2.8 bottles of Campari.