This is the payroll recording for December 1st, 2025
to December 7th, 2025.
Gonna start with the Monday AM shift.
It was just Brooke Neal solo.
So this is final numbers, $82 and 52 cents.
Again, Monday AM, Brooke Neal, $82 and 52 cents.
Monday PM was Austin Kelly.
These are before tip-out numbers.
He made $143.95, but he needs to tip out Ryan, $15.86.
So we need to do that calculation.
Tuesday AM was Brooke Neal just solo.
So these are the final numbers, $12 and 4 cents.
Tuesday PM was Austin Kelly just solo.
So these are the final numbers, $129 and 85 cents.
$129 and 85 cents.
Onto Wednesday, excuse me, December 3rd, 2025.
It was Brooke Neal just by herself solo.
So these are the final numbers, $94 and 1 cent.
Onto Wednesday PM shift.
It was Kevin Worley and he had support staff.
So these are the before tip-out numbers, $68 and 10 cents.
Then he needs to tip out Ryan, $9 and 95 cents.
Onto Thursday AM shift.
It was Austin Kelly just solo.
So these are the final numbers, $120 and 8 cents.
Onto, excuse me, that last report
was the only report for Thursday.
Austin Kelly was solo all day long
and his final tip numbers for all of Thursday,
and these are all the tips all day, $120 and 8 cents.
Onto Friday morning.
It was Austin Kelly and he was solo, so no tip-out.
These are the final numbers, $56 and 6 cents.
Onto Friday PM shift.
It was Austin Kelly, excuse me.
Again, for the Friday PM shift, it was Austin Kelly
and he did have a support staff.
So these are before tip-out numbers, $59 and 73 cents.
And he needs to tip out Fiona Dodson, $10 and 40 cents.
All right, onto Saturday.
This is actually all day.
So these numbers are the final numbers for Saturday all day.
Kevin Worley, $93 and 83 cents.
Mark, $93 and 83 cents.
Ryan was the utility guy, $11 and 82 cents.
Onto Sunday morning.
Mike was solo, so these are final tip numbers, $116 and 44 cents.
Onto Sunday PM, so that was the AM shift.
Now onto Sunday PM shift, December 7th, 2025.
It was Kevin Worley just solo,
so these are the final tip numbers, $58 and 76 cents.