This is the payroll recording for December 8th, 2025 through December 14th, 2025.
Getting started here with the Monday, December 18th AM shift.
It was Brooke Neal solo.
So no tip out.
Her final tips for the Monday AM shift are $128.23.
Again, those are final numbers for Monday AM.
Now on to Monday PM shift.
Austin Kelly.
This is his before tip out number.
$299.80.
And he needs to tip out Ryan Alexander $32.82.
On to Tuesday, December 9th, 2025.
This is the AM shift.
Brooke was solo.
So these are the final tip numbers.
$64.55.
On to the Tuesday PM shift.
It was Austin Kelly.
And these are the before tip out numbers.
So before tip out, Austin made $116.62.
But he needs to tip out Ryan Alexander $16.99.
Now on to Wednesday, December 10th, 2025 was Brooke Neal.
And these are the before tip out numbers.
$156.88.
And she needs to tip out Ryan Alexander $20.
Now on to the Wednesday, December 10th, 2025 PM shift.
These are the final numbers.
Kevin Worley, $288.84 after tip out.
Ryan Alexander $41.25.
Now on to Thursday, December 11th, 2025.
This is the AM shift.
It was Austin Kelly solo.
So these are the final after tip out numbers.
$140.02 after final numbers.
On to Thursday, December 11th, 2025 PM shift.
It was Austin Kelly.
These are before tip out numbers because Ryan was the utility guy.
So before tip out, Austin Kelly made $104.17.
But he needs to tip out Ryan Alexander $16.49.
Now on to Friday, December 12th, 2025.
Before tip out on Friday, December 12th, 2025 AM shift.
Austin Kelly before tip out made $221.88.
But he needs to tip out Ryan Alexander $18.93.
And for the PM shift, it was, let's see, so servers.
And these are before tip out numbers.
So we need to do the calculation like with the other before tip out ones.
Austin Kelly before tip out $414.78 needs to tip out Ryan Alexander $49.34.
Kevin Worley before tip out $156.84.
And he needs to tip out $17.99.
This was a tip pool, so Austin and Kevin need to make an equivalent number of tips after tip out.
Now on to Saturday, December 13th, 2025.
This is the AM shift.
And Kevin and Austin were tip pooling.
First I'll do Kevin. And again, so these are the before tip out numbers.
So we need to do the calculation for that.
And remember, again, Kevin and Austin are tip pooling here.
Kevin Worley total tips and fees before tip out $151.80 needs to tip out Ryan $24.74.
Austin Kelly $227.11 needs to tip out Ryan $40.55.
Then Kevin also did a mid shift here.
And this is, there's no tip out here.
So this is the final numbers.
$122.72. And this was for Kevin's mid shift.
So we can just add these numbers to the PM.
But these numbers, that $122.72, again, that's a final number.
And it's not tip pooling. Kevin is keeping all of that.
Now on to Saturday, December 13th, 2025.
This is the PM shift.
Here are the final after tip out numbers.
Actually, wait, never mind. These are before tip out numbers.
So we need to do this calculation.
But they were tip pooling. So it needs to be equal.
And when I say they are tip pooling, I'm only referring to the front of house employees.
Mark's tips before tip out were $149.09.
He needs to tip out Ryan Alexander $25.89.
Kevin Worley before tip out made $125.
But he needs to tip out Ryan Alexander $13.56.
Again, Mark and Kevin were tip pooling there.
We need to keep that in mind when doing the calculation.
Now on to Sunday, December 14th, 2025.
These are the final numbers. Mark Baryanek $115.31.
Mike Walton $115.31.
Ryan Alexander $17.22.
Again, those were just the final numbers for that day.
Excuse me, for the AM shift, not for the day as a whole.
Just for the Sunday AM shift.
Now for the Sunday PM shift.
Here are the final numbers. Mark Baryanek $142.00.
Ryan Alexander $25.65.